Hi, I'm JK Dooley, I'm a professional artist, and today we're talking a little bit about giclee reproduction.
And now we're talking about canvas, and choosing canvas to have your prints done on.
The nice thing about actually canvas and paper is there are really a lot of sizes that you can choose from.
As you can see, we've got three different sizes here, kind of small, medium, and large.
But, you're basically only limited by the size of your printer.
So there are printers, mine takes up to 42 inches wide.
So that means your piece can be pretty wide, by as long as the roll of canvas is.
There are printers that are up to 60 inches wide.
So, if you wanting to reproduce a large piece, this is a great way to do it.
And, probably apiece that large, you're definitely going to want to do on canvas, because it is more durable, and it will hold up better.
So, there's a lot of options here, you can go a lot of different sizes, which means you can meet a lot of your customer's needs.
You can take custom orders, you can print an image perhaps that you've painted small, you can print it really big, and that's always kind of fun to do as well.
So, that's one of the really nice things about this process, is you can be very versatile when it comes to choosing sizes.